Yoselson, Kathy Clever Hans Bakery and Oasis Natural Grocery Unionization Papers 6392
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kathy Yoselson Clever Hans Bakery and Oasis Natural Grocery Unionization Papers
1981-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Yoselson, Kathy
6392
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
.
8646493
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 23, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6400m: Tom Walls Clever Hans Workers Association Union Drive Papers
Ithaca, NY; Golder, Neil; Yoselson, Kathryn; Clever Hans Bakery; National Labor Relations Board (NLRB); Oasis Natural Grocery; United Auto Workers (UAW), Local 2300
8646493
- Agreement between Clever Hans Bakery and Workers Association, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Clever Hans Job Descriptions, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Clever Hans Staff Manuel, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clever Hans Workers' Association Administration Papers, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clever Hans Workers' Association Handwritten Negotiation Notes (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Clever Hans Workers' Association Notebooks, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Clever Hans Workers' Association Handbook, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Clever Hans Labor Practices Case: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-11067, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Clever Hans Unfair Labor Practices Case: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-12167, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Unfair Labor Practices Case: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-12075, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Clever Hans Unfair Labor Practice Case: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-12223, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Clever Hans Unfair Labor Practice Case: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-12243, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Amended Complaint: NLRB Case No. 3-CA-12243, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NLBR Order Further Consolidating Clever Hans Cases, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Clever Hans Workers' Association Publicity and News Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Clever Hans Re-organization as Employee-Owner (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Recipes (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Clever Hans Contract Draft, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agreement Between Oasis Natural Grocery and UAW Local 2300, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Oasis Natural Grocery and UAW Local 2300 Original Signed Contract, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Agreement Between Oasis Natural Grocery and UAW Local 2300, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Agreement Between Oasis Natural Grocery and UAW Local 2300, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Agreement Between Oasis Natural Grocery and UAW Local 2300, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Oasis Management: Anti-Union Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Anti-Union Literature, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Oasis Memos From Management, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Union Literature, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- UAW Pamphlets and Flyers, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Letters Supporting the UAW Local 2300 Organizing Drive at Oasis, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Oasis Union Vote Challengers: NLRB Case No. 3-RC-9881, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Oasis Workers' Association Union Vote Notes, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Oasis Union Recognition, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Oasis Employee Issue Survey (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Oasis Workers' Contract Survey, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Oasis Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Peggy Aker, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bill Deats, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Jane Kennedy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Dolores Sayet (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Notes from May 5, 1992 with Owners (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Oasis NLRB Documents, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Oasis Unfair Labor Practices, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- NLRB Affidavits, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Oasis NLRB Subpoena, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Oasis Letter of Concern (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Oasis Possible Grievances for Dayle, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Oasis Grievances, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Oasis Seniority, Layoff, Grievance, Discipline, Job Vacancies, and Training, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UAW Local 2300 General Grievance Notes, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Oasis Personal (Restricted) Warnings, 1994-2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Oasis Unemployment Insurance Appeal Mia Finkeldey, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Oasis Health and Safety, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Oasis Contact Health and Safety Proposals (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Oasis Employee Lists (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Oasis Telephone Lists, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Oasis Personnel Policies, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Oasis Sales, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Oasis Sales, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Oasis Deli, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Oasis Publicity, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Oasis Contract Proposals, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Oasis Workers' Association Bargaining, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Oasis Workers' Negotiations, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Oasis Workers' Association Updates from Bargaining Terms, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Oasis Time Clock Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- UAW Local 2300 Letters to Oasis Management, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Notes on Wage Negotiations, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Oasis UAW Local 2300 Bargaining, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- UAW Local 2300 Guide for New Members, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- UAW Local 2300 Information Packet (Box 2, Folder 25)
- UAW Arbitration Department, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- UAW Local 2300's Finances, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- UAW Constitution, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- AL's Oasis File, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Notes to Al Davidoff (Box 2, Folder 30)
- UAW Local 2300 Executive Board, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- UAW Local 2300 Polling Places (Box 2, Folder 32)
- UAW Local 2300 Press Releases, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- UAW Local 2300 By-Laws, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- UAW Local 2300 Notes on Arbitration (Box 2, Folder 35)
- UAW Local 2300 Notes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- UAW, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Oasis Workers' Association Minute Book, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- UAW Local 2300 Minute Book, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- UAW Local 2300 Minute Book, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- UAW Local 2300 Minute Books, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- UAW Local 2300 Minute Book, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UAW Local 2300 Minute Book, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Somadhara Partnership Structure, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Articles on Employee Ownership, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Kathy's Notes, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Green Star, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kathy's Employment at Greenstar, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- GreenStar Oasis Restructuring, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Other Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Lakeside Nursing Home, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- UAW Local 2300 Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1991-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- UAW Local 2300 NLRB Case No. 3-RC-10198: American Red Cross, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- UAW Local 2300 Small Units, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- UAW Local 2300 and AIDS Work of Tompkins County, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Somadhara Newsletters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Health and Safety for Office Workers, 1991-2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- The Vocal Local 2300, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- The Bear Facts, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)